[Music] I
will say this but everyone knows that Stand Allo
Health is an Eras company, due to which
no medical need is fulfilled.
Present to talk to us is
ICICI Health Agency Vice President
Amrish Save. You are very welcome to Sash Today.
Today you have briefed the media. Are
you bringing some unique initiative in
front of the customers, sir? Thank
you. So our new health office is
called Elevate and Elevate is a health office
which will appeal to all customer segments
because we have included a range of features in it
and they can be personalized. Personalized
means that if you want a short time shot
with some comfort then you can take that, if you want
unlimited time shots then you can also take that.
And the pricing is very good so that it
appeals to every segment.
We have also included some such features in this product
which are industry first, which till date are
not there in any product of the industry,
such features have also been included in it, if
I may say one thing then by taking care of information, a
feature  This is what happens in this,
suppose I have a policy of Rs 10 lakh
but I have a claim of Rs 25 lakh, then
generally this will not be covered in any policy,
you will be covered up to Rs 10 lakh, the above Rs
15 lakh, the customer has to pay from his own pocket,
but this feature of INFAA is
so powerful that a claim up to
INFAA value, any value be it Rs 25 lakh, Rs 35
lakh, Rs 50 lakh up to that value gets
covered under INFAA care, so in this way we
have three-four innovative features which
give complete care, complete comfort
to the customer, saying that if I take this feature, then if
any such incident or accident occurs,
it will be covered, how much AI has been
used in this, sir, and
what is the efficiency and accuracy rate, good
question, so in this, as I told you, there
is a recommendation engine of Artificial Intelligence, so what does this engine do, which
comes from customer segment, many
different customer profiles  Let us differentiate, for
example, if there is a single individual who has just started working, let's say he is
27 years old,
his needs are different, a
32 year old who is about to get married has
different needs from a 36 year old who has just got married
and just got married with one child, so such
customer segments are very different,
so what we have done is through
artificial intelligence, we have said that
we will give some recommendations from our side,
based on where you are going to live,
what is your family size, what is your requirement, up
to what limit do you need coverage, we will
recommend you a set of features
which we think you should take, now
artificial intelligence works as an engine
and will recommend you that
you should take this, but this is
not mandatory, this is good to have and
this is recommendation, but not mandatory, one it comes
to accuracy, there is a far deeper
study which  We have done this before we have given this
recommendation because we have looked
at customer profiles, we have looked at our
own data, we have looked at what customers
buy and what they want to buy, on that basis we have given this
recommendation, I would say it is too early to see how
accurate this is and what is the accuracy
percentage, but as we go forward we will be able to see what is
the usage and uptake,
we will probably be able to find out, sir, this
entire service that you are
offering to the customers, what is the research in it, were there
any parameters on which you did
research, after that you brought this product,
so if I talk about health insurance in India,
firstly its penetration
is very low, secondly the products are very
fixed that this is the plan you have to take,
and what is bought today, that may not be
sufficient 15 years down the
line, this means that today the plan worth Rs 10 lakh  The sum
assured that I have taken a sum assured, after 15 years, the
normal expenses have
quadrupled. So, my Rs 10 lakh
plan is not going to be good enough because
we know how medical expenses
and hospital expenses are increasing.
So, we have included such features in it that will give you the
comfort that
even after 15 years, if I get a large claim, how am I covered? So, the
power booster
feature, what happens in the power booster is that
if I have taken a sum assured of Rs 10 lakh today, every
year it will increase by 100%, so next
year it will be Rs 20 lakh, the year after that it will be Rs
30 lakh, so in 10 years, my
policy of Rs 10 lakh today will become Rs 1 crore. So, this gives the
comfort to the customer that in future,
if I get a big claim and even
the expenses have increased, but still it will get covered.
Elevate is
a very strong feature which gives
complete peace of mind to the customer. So, another very
important aspect is that today's product is
for the customer. As I told you, it
is a very fixed plan, but the features here are that the
customer can pick and choose if he
wants to take a time shot of Rs 10 lakh
and also get insurance cover or if he
says no, I want to get
insurance cover today itself, then he can take it in the base plan itself. So,
this is the range of features, it has 22
to 25 features which the customer can pick and choose. It will be
very interesting if the customer really
wants to get a deeper understanding of the
product and buying features. So, it is a very
good product. Now let's talk about the
terms and conditions, sir. What are the terms and conditions of this policy,
sir? Okay, so just like there is a
regular health insurance, there are a lot of
features that tell you that this works like this. This
works like this. There is a
waiting period.  So, in this product
there is a three year waiting period that when
you enter the product, after one year all your
illnesses will be covered.
In many products there is an
entry age, in this product there is no
entry age, you can enter at any age, so this is a
very strong feature, some
products say that you can enter till 65, some
till 75, so here in this feature
in this product there is no entry, so there are many
features, but I would say that
a customer and any intermediary or channel
partner, when they offer this, they should discuss
and disclose all the terms and conditions that are there
and like I said that in fact,
when I was telling you that during the entire
life of the policy you
can take only one claim of the infeit value, so it should
not be assumed that I will get one
infeit claim every year, so it is very important to know the terms and conditions
and this is where it is, I think,
so inform cell which is available today.
We use the word 'bahut
important hai' (inform sale should happen)
Sir, the last question about all the
competition is why are you best in the
business. Okay, so in health insurance,
you know most of the product lines, as per
IIDA's published figures,
in the private sector, we are the
number one company. If you look at our recently
announced motor, you know market
share, we are again leading in most of the
product lines on the SME front,
we are number one on the motor front. And with the same intention,
we have launched this Elevate product, that we want to be
extremely
competitive and we want to have a very
good product offering over here. Also,
with the same intention, we have launched Elevate, that as we
move forward, we are you know
doing very good business in health. And the more
important aspect is can we cover more
customers, can we give that peace of mind to
most customers.  Those who want to join us,
whether they consider IC's health
insurance policy as a great policy,
they want to take it, that is the whole intention
of having this product.